# ZIAD HOSNY

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

ziadhosny007@gmail.com

(+2) 01110146112

ziadhosny.vercel.app

in <u>LinkedIn</u>

<u>GitHub</u>

Egypt

#### PROFILE

I have 2+ years of Experience in Analyzing, Designing, Developing and Integrating Front-End & Back-End based applications. Experience in developing application using TypeScript, React, ReactNative, NodeJs, Express. Seeking a role as Front-end and Nodejs Developer

### EXPERIENCE

Jul 2022 - Jun 2023 Bitspire Company - Full stack Developer (React And Nodejs).

Developing frontend and backend websites using React, Node and I am responsible for developing new features and user interfaces from wireframe models, ensuring the best performance and user experience of the software, fixing bugs and performance problems, writing clean, readable, and testable code, cooperating with back-end developers, designers.

Jun 2023 - Jun 2023 eSmart Company - Front-end Developer.

responsible for Creating And Developing a calendar for the clinic system by picking and rescheduling suitable dates for doctors' appointments.

Jun 2023 - Now Shoaa Company - Full stack Developer (React And Nodejs).

Worked on multiple full-stack service projects for calculating the consumption of electricity, installing and fixing electricity meters, and following up with customers, I am working with a great team to plan, cooperate, implement projects, and deliver them at the highest level

# EDUCATION

Apr 2022 - Sep 2022 Information Technology Institute

Front-End & Cross-Platform Intensive Code Camp

2016 - 2020 Mansoura University

**BSc in Computers and Information** - Mansoura University. (Grade: Very Good).

Graduation Project: Building a mobile learning app with a chatbot by Android, Java, Python, and NLP.

# SKILLS

- React

- NodeJs

- JavaScript

- TypeScript

- Docker

- React Native

- Tailwind CSS

- Express

- Nestis

- Bootstrap

- Angular

- Postgres

- MySql

- Git

- CI CD

- Python

- Nextis

- MonogoDB

# P E R S O N A L S K I L L S

- Continuous improvement

- Good communication

- Team Work

- Problem solving

- Self Learning

#### LANGUAGES

- English : Professional

- Arabic: Native

### $\mathbf{E}$

# Portfolio 🔗 🔘





My portfolio shows my progress, skills, and latest projects, You can contact me through it. Build Using NextJs, TypeScript, React, MUI, CSS

# Advanced Audio Player 🔗



Full project for playing audios and soundtracks, Play audios randomly or on repeat. with a cool feature that makes you select a specific part of the audio and insert the number of times you want to play it, log in, and make your favorite list. Build using GatsbyJs, React, Node, Express, Postgresql, Sass

#### <u>Scheduler</u>



React And JS Library Calender for clinic System by picking and rescheduling dates for doctors' appointments by Inserting or dragging dates, Adding more information about the date, and disabling holidays, which is suitable for any booking system with high performance and easy-to-use features.

Build using React, Typescript, Javascript, date-fns, MUI

# Task Manager



Full Task Manager with a Nice user interface in which you can add, check tasks, and pick due dates for accomplishing tasks with filter, Edit, and delete features.

Build using React, Redux, Node, MongoDB, Express, MUI, CSS

# Freshio





ITI Graduation project E-commerce for buying healthy products and protein supplies, With Categories and filters to pick products according to price and Calories per product, I was the team leader who designed and chose the suitable solutions for this project with high-performance and maintainable software.

Build using React, MUI, Bootstrap, and Firebase.